Welcome to Udemy. I just want to make sure that you are ready to use the tools correctly
to maximize learning potential. So in this course, I will be speaking at my normal speed.
But if you think I am too slow, you can speed me up up to 2x.
Oppositely, if you think I speak too fast, you can decrease my speed up to 0.5x.
Also, I've made sure that this course has professional subtitles,
which you can enable on the bottom right using the CC icon.
Finally, you can also use transcripts to read alongside the video if that helps you maximize your
learning. At some point during the course, Udemy will ask you for some feedback.
If you are not ready to give a rating yet, click on Ask Me Later.
Else, you can select a star rating for whatever you want, and then click on the star when
you're done. Here, you can leave me a small message telling me what you'd like about this course
and what you want me to improve. When you're done, click on 7 continue, and you can go ahead
with this course. I want to say ratings are super important for me and for new students,
So please make sure you leave one when you're ready.
Okay, that's all I will see you in the next lecture.